I love all dogs.
I do.
But what is it with people buying designer dogs?
People want to be trendy.
They want a dog that fits the aesthetic.
But you know what doesn't fit the aesthetic?
Buying dogs who can't breathe.
You've heard of breathing impaired breeds, right?
Well, these are dogs who have been unnaturally bred and inbred to have flattened faces,
making it difficult for them to breathe.
They also require extensive and expensive medical care just to help them take in air.
Why are people spending thousands of dollars on designer dogs who can't breathe?
By adopting from a shelter and not supporting breeders,
you can send the message that breeding dogs to suffer is not the vibe.
Plus, when you adopt, you can find an awesome mutt like Jordy.
Hi, Jordy!
You can help stop the demand for designer and breathing impaired dogs by adopting your next dog
and finding a companion almost as trendy as Jordy.
Look at that mohawk.
For more ways to help animals, visit PETA.org.